hello everyone this is ey on ey censored
Supernatural Bible changes on YouTube
and today is January 9th
2024 and I want to go ahead and give you
a little bit of information about this
book this is um the second book that I
wrote called Supernatural Bible changes
Satan's tricks and lying signs and
wonders you can purchase this on Amazon
and it was published in December I have
another book The abomination of
desolation Supernatural Bible changes my
first book that I published a year ago
that's also available on
Amazon what I wanted to do in this book
and what I did is I gave more
information a lot more
information and I cover what's happening
to scripture I'm going to show you my
manuscript here and you can see here
I'll zoom in here I have an
introduction I have a a brief chapter on
you must be born again Jesus Christ is a
word of God and you can read all these
different topics here that I have in my
book I want to tell you what I've done
here so you understand where I was
coming from I after 7 and 1/2 years of
studying what's happening to our Bibles
I began seeing Trends I began seeing
agendas that were being woven into
scripture to prepare the way for the
Antichrist and it became very early it
became really apparent to me very early
on that this was the abomination of
desolation standing in the Holy place
and He who reads let him
understand and I realized that in 2
Thessalonians 2 we were warned that the
Antichrist I'm going to go ahead and
paraphrase this the Antichrist will
essentially pretend that he is God and
he will blaspheme God and there will be
a great falling away and people will
basically end up worshiping the
Beast these are lying signs and wonders
that we're seeing happen in our Bibles
and there are many other things that are
happening around
us we all know that but I focus on the
Bible changes because of the Eternal
consequence so these segmentations that
I'm going to share with you you have a
slew of scripture verses that I'm I put
in these tables along with the the word
or words and then the Strong's number so
that you as a Berean as a seeker of
Truth can go to say Blue Letter Bible
and type in either the word the
scripture verse or the Strong's number
and get more
information very important that you take
what I'm saying seriously and that you
study this research this pray and fast
and seek the Lord ask him to open up
your eyes because the Bible now has
grammar errors punctuation errors new
words nonsense versus doctrinal errors
emoticons new people modern words words
erased and on and on it goes the changes
are self-evident now what I want to
point out and make it very clear is that
the enemy the Antichrist wants to take
dominion over
everything every factor of our lives
here on
Earth and we're seeing this happen in
real time if you have the eyes to see
and so what I see in
scripture are
words that well let me show you the
first one this is alphabetized
agriculture food and
Wildlife there there are new words
related to each of those
three and when you read these verses
they're wholly different for example we
now have corn in the Bible how
ridiculous is that we now have new
animals in the Bible like apes now I'm
talking about the King James Bible but
every English Bible has new animals and
new Foods in it and new agriculture I'm
talking about plants trees that we've
never heard of before we even have
melons in the King James Bible cucumbers
garlic spelled with a K
misspelled we have words like um meat
that's been
multiplied me e a t me T and me
te are now in scripture and the word
meat has definitely been multiplied in
the Bible corn is
ridiculous it was grain we still have
grain in the Bible but I think it's less
than 10
times and on and on it goes so that is
that segmentation that's that particular
grouping then I have a table for alcohol
and
drugs you heard me correctly we now have
alcohol and drugs in our
Bibles Alien Invasion we have a lot of
words related to Alien Invasion space
travel now in the
Bible Catholicism is another agenda
because we're seeing doctrinal changes
that align itself to
Catholicism we know that Catholicism is
a cult it absolutely is we even have
saints in the Old Testament did you know
that
yeah the first saint was found in the
Old
Testament I think it was
Aaron but we have like Holy Father in
the Bible now holy Child
Jesus and on and on it goes there are
many more so that's that
segmentation climate change that's right
climate change the green agenda is in
the Bible such as pollute pollution
Environ and many other new words in the
Bible Commerce and
jobs we now have the word unemployment
no excuse me um we now have words like
town clerk lawyers doctors Physicians
nurses in the
Bible and that list is really long for
Commerce and
jobs and again I think it has to do do
with the influence the satanic influence
over these jobs and businesses you'll
understand when you read these lists or
at least I pray in the name of Jesus
your eyes will be
open education we now have school in the
Bible we have the word College in the
Bible we have scholars in the Bible and
on and on it goes there just just a few
new
words Financial we now have a bank in
the Bible a financial bank we have new
currency in the Bible and many many
other new words related to
finance Freemasonry a lot of new Masonic
terms are now plopped into the Bible
like aprons Adam and Eve are now wearing
aprons in the Bible and there are many
other new words in in the Bible
associated with Freemasonry that are new
holiday time we have the new word
holiday in the Bible h o l y d a y in
the Bible and it's related believe it or
not to the pilgrimage to Mecca according
to the
concordance on non it goes holiday time
household we have new words related to
our house houses like Furniture we even
have camels Furniture in the
Bible we have words like parlor Cottage
and so forth now in
scripture
humans would you believe the word humans
are now in different English
Bibles also I think Humanity was another
one that I found but we also have words
like liver in our Bibles we have
the word fingers have been multiplied in
scripture um and on and on it
goes incredible and I will tell you not
to scare you but our B our bodies are
also changing through this nefarious
witchcraft I do not understand I think
it's through
frequencies but at the end of the day
it's all witchcraft our hearts have
moved our hearts used to be on the left
side of our bodies now our heart is in
the middle our kidneys that's another
new word in the Bible our kidneys used
to be in our lower back now they are in
the middle of our
back and on and on it
goes I also have an Islamic segment here
and I did create a small
book focus on Islam now invading
scripture Mormon there is definitely a
Mormon agenda in the rewriting of our
Bibles you have to remember there the
enemy wants to bring everything together
to worship Him okay so we have Mormon
words in the Bible like
Ward Bishop prick how offensive is that
and on and on it goes multisyllabic new
words that sound
Arabic crazy new
words mythological and fairy tales we
now have words like unicorn Matrix
prancing horses and on and on it goes in
our Bibles
pandemics that's right this one is huge
and I'm actually in the middle of
creating well I should say almost
finishing a book on the words related to
pandemic now in the Bible and
um this is related to all the new um
everything related to what we've seen in
the last few years related to the plan
demics right and um it's crazy
that is really crazy but again it's
witchcraft so I believe as they're
changing scripture they're either
sending messages to each other or is and
either or releasing demons and by the
way the word demons and Demon have been
erased from the King James
Bible all changed to devil and Devil's
plural that's
right politics and Military that was
another huge segment because we have new
words related to politics and Military
now in the Bible for example we now have
believe it or not the word liberal in
the
Bible and we have the word Publican in
the Bible we have presidents Senators
Senate and on and on it goes in our
Bibles
today royalty there's a royal theme
going on in scripture castles
Greyhound um princes have been
multiplied and on on it goes Sports we
now have words related to Sports in the
Bible even the word Sport and sporting
now in the King James Bible technology
believe it or not we have devices in the
Bible witty
inventions and other words related to
technology in scripture to day travel we
now have new countries in the King James
Bible along with different forms of
transportation like a fairy boat now in
the Old
Testament witchcraft lots of words
related to Witchcraft and the Occult now
in the Bible including like Words
related to Spirit cooking
cannibalism and so forth absolutely
Wicked
Wicked language has been inserted into
scripture and it's time to wake up in
jesus' name my last segment was the woke
culture I would call this Sodom and
Gomorrah Wicked and
perverse language being inserted in a
scripture that's manifesting in the
world around us men now have breasts
full of milk they're nursing fathers in
the Bible men are wearing skirts and
aprons and bonnets and Turles and on on
it
goes so this is really lengthy I gave
you a few examples for each of these
segments and there is a lot more to
share with you so I hope that helps you
understand the contents of this book you
can find this book on Amazon it's $20
paperback $10 on Kindle you can download
this book today if you want
to or order it paperback and I pray that
this book will be a blessing for you as
difficult as this subject matter is it's
so harrowing it's so disturbing it's
so
lifechanging and you're going to have
different emotions as you research this
from
anger to horror to disbelief to laughter
there are times when you will read these
new verses and you will literally find
yourself in an
uncontrollable laughing fit out of
horror embarrassment disbelief I've been
there I've cried I've been angry I've
laughed over 7 and a half years studying
this
material and it's undeniable and it's
time to wake up in jesus' name I do have
many other books that I have written
that I will continue I will do briefings
like this with each book um and you can
find all my books on Amazon also on my
website
bang.com you can find these on my first
page and then also just in case I do
have a tab of books and journals that I
have created that are available on
Amazon with that said I want to give
thanks to everybody in the community for
praying for me supporting my channel
encouraging me and
also um helping me to see the changes
because of course I have to say this has
been a a community
involvement and many of you over the
years have contacted me with words that
you have seen um changes that you see in
scripture and I want to go ahead and
honor that as well what's most important
to any person who's seeking out this
matter is to one get right with Jesus
Christ you must must be born again to
enter the Kingdom of Heaven two you need
to understand this is really happening
and not be afraid to search out the
matter I do not want any person who's
seeking truth to be deceived and I
believe
that it's so blatantly obvious to me
that this is truly the strong delusion
and so not everybody will have eyes to
see or ears to hear this they have been
blinded because the Bible says that God
would send the strong delusion because
they did not love the truth so how do we
counteract that we pray that our
our that the Christians would have a
love for the truth and even
non-christians that they non-christians
would be brought to repentance and life
in Christ but we need to pray that the
church would have a hunger and a thirst
for truth because in seeking truth the
changes scripture are truly
self-evident feel free to email me if
you have any questions at ey report
gmail.com thank you so much again for
praying for me
and just
your encouragement brothers and sisters
may God bless you and your families in
jesus'
name